const qBank = [
	{
		id: 1,
		question: "When is the World Population Day observed?",
		options: ["July 11", "July 12", "May 11", "June 11"],
		answer: "July 11",
	},
	{
		id: 2,
		question: "World Human Rights Day is observed on",
		options: ["December 10", "December 7", "September 5", "September 10"],
		answer: "December 10",
	},
	{
		id: 3,
		question: "The year 1985 was declared as the International Year of",
		options: ["Blind", "Children", "GandhiWomen", "Youth"],
		answer: "Youth"
	},
	{
		id: 4,
		question: "The birthday of which of the leader in India is observed as Children's day?",
		options: ["Mahatma Gandhi", "S.Radhakrishnan", "Rajiv Gandhi", "Jawaharlal Nehru"],
		answer: "Jawaharlal Nehru"
	},
	{
		id: 5,
		question: "Which day is observed as World Food Day?",
		options: ["September 16", "August 16", "November 4", "October 16"],
		answer: "October 16"
	},
	{
		id: 6,
		question: "When is the National Youth Day observed?",
		options: ["September 16", "January 12", "February 13", "October 12"],
		answer: "January 12"
	},
    {
		id: 7,
		question: "When is the National Education Day observed?",
		options: ["11th Nov", "10th Nov", "11th Sep", "21th Nov"],
		answer: "11th Nov"
	},
	
	{
		id: 8,
		question: "When is the National Science Day  observed?",
		options: ["29th Feb", "30th March", "28th Feb", "20th March"],
		answer: "28th Feb"
	},
	{
		id: 9,
		question: "Teacher's day is observed on which of the date?",
		options: ["3rd January", "5th Oct", "5th July", "None of the above"],
		answer: "None of the above"
	},
	{
		id: 10,
		question: "World Environment day is celebrated on  _____________________.",
		options: ["5th January", "5th Oct", "5th July", "5th June"],
		answer: "5th June"
	},
	{
		id: 11,
		question: "29th July is celebrated as  _____________________?",
		options: ["International Nurse Day", "International Women's Day", "International Dance Day", "International Tiger Day"],
		answer: "International Tiger Day"
	},
	{
		id: 12,
		question: "When is the National Ayurveda Day observed?",
		options: ["28th Oct", "18th Oct", "4th Nov", "8th Nov"],
		answer: "28th Oct"
	},
	{
		id: 13,
		question: "National Engineerâ€™s Day is celebrated on _______________ .",
		options: ["15th Sep", "18th Oct", "15th Nov", "5th Nov"],
		answer: "15th Sep"
	},
	{
		id: 14,
		question: "When is the World Ozone Day observed?",
		options: ["12th Oct", "16th Sep", "5th July", "None of the above"],
		answer: "16th Sep"
	},
	{
		id: 15,
		question: "The year 1991 was observed in India as the year of",
		options: ["Population control", "Girl child", "Literacy", "Tourism"],
		answer: "Tourism"
	},
	{
		id: 16,
		question: "'International Yoga Day' is observed on _____ ?",
		options: ["22nd July", "21st June", "21st April", "11th June"],
		answer: "21st June"
	},
	{
		id: 17,
		question: "When is National girl child day of India?",
        options: ["24th July", "24th June", "21st April", "24th Jan"],
		answer: "24th Jan"
	},
	{
		id: 18,
		question: "Navy day is observed  on ________",
		options: ["4th June", "4th March", "4th Oct", "4th Dec"],
		answer: "4th Dec"
	},
	{
		id: 19,
		question: "When is International Day of Families observed?",
		options: ["May 15th", "May 16th", "May 14th", "May 13th"],
		answer: "May 15th"
	},
	{
		id: 20,
		question: "'World Television Day' is observed every year on ___.",
		options: ["Nov 21st", "Oct 21st", "Nov 22nd", "Aug 22nd"],
		answer: "Nov 21st"
	},
	{
		id: 21,
		question: "When is the earth day celebrated?",
		options: ["April 22nd", "April 27th", "June 5th", "June 22nd"],
		answer: "April 22nd"
	},
	{
		id: 22,
		question: "November 30 is observed as _________",
		options: ["Computer Security Day", "International Cooperative Day", "World Vegetarian Day", "None of the above"],
		answer: "Computer Security Day"
	},
	{
		id: 23,
		question: "World Health Day is observed on ________",
		options: ["April 14", "April 7", "April 17", "April 28"],
		answer: "April 7"
	},
	{
		id: 24,
		question: "October 24 is observed as__________",
		options: ["World Immunization Day", "United Nations Day", "World Environment Day", "World Immunization Day"],
		answer: "United Nations Day"
	},
	{
		id: 25,
		question: "World Blood Donar Day is observed on ___________",
		options: ["June 14", "April 17", "Aug 14", "Feb 8"],
		answer: "June 14"
	},
]

export default qBank;
